

JUNIOR FRONT END DEVELOPER

Details

+38 (099) 039 45 74 sergey.garmash09@gmail.com

Links

linkedin

GitHub

Skype

Telegram

Skills

HTML5

CSS3

Sass

Bootstrap 4

JavaScript

jQuery

Git

Word Press

OpenCart

Languages

Ukrainian

English

Profile

I am a front-end developer with a lot of love for my work. I have about 3 years of commercial experience

Worked with various technologies (CMS) systems such as WordPress (woo-commerce), OpenCart . I have experience in development both from scratch and development in an existing project.

I own a number of technologies such as HTML5 and CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery

Employment History

Resty App, Html / Css Developer, Kharkiv

JANUARY 2019 - DECEMBER 2019

Worked as a markup developer.

- 1. Developed emails using the Foundation for Emails framework and the MJML framework.
- 2. Developed sites on WordPress. Corporate websites on WordPress, and also using the woocommerce plugin.

Examples of work:

Financial: https://financialmindfulness.com/

Freelance, Front end / Wordpress developer, Kharkiv

FEBRUARY 2020 - JUNE 2020

- 1. Engaged in landing page layout and using the Bootstrap and Foundation frameworks
- 2. Was engaged in the development of sites on WordPress (CMS) as corporate sites and using the woocommerce plugin.

Examples of work:

Hydromea: https://www.hydromea.com/

ValidPath: https://join.validpath.co.uk/

Front end, Intertool, Kharkiv

AUGUST 2020 - JANUARY 2022

Worked as a Front end Developer

- 1. Worked in a team to develop an online store for wholesale and retail trade based on CMS OpenCart version 3.0.3.2, Bootstrap, JQuery, SCSS/SASS, PHP template engine for HTML Twig
- 2. Worked in a team on the development of a restaurant and hotel complex based on OpenCart version 2.0, Bootstrap, JQuery, SCSS/SASS
- 3. Worked in the development team of an online retail store. The store was written without the use of CMS and third-party frameworks, and the JQuery JavaScript library was used to work with the DOM.

Education

KHADI, Kharkiv

OCTOBER 2010 - OCTOBER 2012

Kharkov Automobile and Road Institute, Kharkov State Automobile and Road Technical University

Courses

Art Jocker, PHP Developer

JULY 2021 - NOVEMBER 2021